adcrax.com 2015-05-02

# ADCraX - Smart Advertising Network | Monetize Website Traffic

## Privacy Policy

ADCraX is a Global Mobile Ad Network and is into business of Mobile Advertising through its Mobile Ad Serving Platform.This document covers the privacy policy of ADCraX which applies to the WAPS/APPS on Mobile where we serve ads. Our Privacy Policy explains how we and some of the companies we work with collect, use, share and protect information in relation to our mobile services, web site, and any software provided on or in connection with ADCraX services and your choices about the collection and use of your information. 

## Information collected by ADCraX

We may collect certain information from the user’s device during ad serving/interaction, which may include following: User Agent Network provider Internet (IP) address Device identifier Media Access Control (MAC) address, Geo location The content type of the ad / genre Media type of the ad ( text, image, video) User interaction events, post click activity of user We may also partner with Data Providers who provide us information which they automatically collect a variety of information associated with your use of your device and our products and services, some of which may be associated with you or another user on your account, which we can help us to improve relevancy of ads and better ads experience. Data about you collected by them is in accordance with their own specific privacy policies and subject to their own applicable legal terms and conditions. We do not intend to use the information provided by them to us for the purpose other than serving you with interest-based ads. 

## Children.

Children. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 18 years of age. If you allow a child to use your device or our services, you should be aware that their personal information could be collected as described in this policy. 

## Information usage

We may use the information we collect to: Display relevant ads based on user deducted interests. Provide filtering options to our affiliates (Developers/Publishers/Associates) To provide targeting options for Advertisers. To help advertisers to avoid serving ads which user has already seen/interacted with/acted upon. We may also use your information for internal purposes, such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our services & content. 

## Information sharing

We may share your information with Advertisers, Developers or other affiliates which will not have any of your PII. We may share the information with an Expert Partner for analysis of data which can helps us in displaying relevant ads and targeting. While sharing information, we will ensure proper hashing/encryption of PII. We use a variety of safeguards to protect the information we collect about you. We will provide user information where necessary to comply with the law, such as disclosure of your information to a law enforcement agency for your safety or the safety of others, or when compelled by subpoena or other legal process. We may share your information to provide, maintain and improve our Services 

## Amendment of Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. The latest Privacy Policy is available on our main website: www.adcrax.com. Please check our Privacy Policy regularly to stay up to date. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator: support@adcrax.com
